paddypowercasino.com 2005-12-14

# Paddy Power Casino - an online casino you can trust

**IMPORTANT: BY USING THIS WEBSITE YOU GIVE YOUR CONSENT THAT ALL PERSONAL DATA SUBMITTED BY YOU MAY BE PROCESSED BY US FOR THE PURPOSES SET OUT BELOW**

We take care to protect the privacy of our customers. This policy explains how we process information about website visitors and those registered with paddypowercasino.com. There are several security features on Our site. Your personal details are protected by firewalls, encryption, and other security measures. Our employees do not have access to your full debit/credit card details. We are committed to the security of your personal details. 

Paddypowercasino.com complies with Data Protection Law (Bailiwick of Guernsey) 2001. In addition, paddypowercasino.com consults the EU privacy laws and the OECD guidelines regularly to ensure the protection of players privacy and transborder data flow. 

Personal information is collated and stored primarily during the registration process, but is also monitored when there is activity on your account and when you use the website. As with many other websites, we may use software known as 'cookies' to store information relating to your preferences to enable us to improve our service to you. 

Personal data submitted by you to paddypowercasino.com will be used for the following purposes only. We will only collect and retain personal data to the extent that it is strictly necessary for one of the following purposes: assisting us in setting up and managing your account; building an accurate customer profile; making information from WagerWare licensees and paddypowercasino.com marketing partners available: and publishing on the website and in other promotional materials, for the purpose of promoting the site, information relating to wins of £10 or more comprising the amount of the win and the abbreviated name, home town, state or province and country of the winner. 

Please note that Paddy Power Alderney Limited, WagerWorks Inc. and the Alderney Gambling Control Commission (AGCC) have access to your account information. However, this information will only be used within the rules and guidelines that govern this site. 

Personal data collected about you when you visit this site will be disclosed only to the following types of persons or partners of paddypowercasino.com; reputable marketing partners selected by us; any company or other entity to whom we may sell all or part of our business; any competent legal, regulatory or law enforcement authority including the AGCC. In the latter case, you will not be informed of any disclosure nor of any reasons for such disclosure and you hereby waive any and all rights that you may have, whether at law or otherwise, of any nature and in any jurisdiction, in connection with such disclosure; our professional advisers or other appropriate third parties, if your use of our service, our Games or this website is in breach of these terms and conditions; and other users of the site and persons receiving promotional materials, in each case pursuant to the information we provide about winners detailed above. 

To make data corrections or to obtain access to the data we have about you, you must send us a written request that should be addressed to the Customer Services Manager for paddypowercasino.com. We will disclose to you your personal data held by us, we shall correct or delete inaccurate details, and notify any third party recipients of the necessary changes. Changes to certain parts of your account information can also be made by accessing 'My Account'. We regularly delete data that is no longer required. 

Paddypowercasino.com is part of the World Wide Web and because of this your personal data may be transferred outside Alderney and the European Economic Area. Whenever such transfers are effected pursuant to arrangements made by us, we shall enter into agreements requiring the recipients of your personal data to adhere to standards of data protection substantially similar to those prevailing in Alderney and the European Economic Area. However, the Internet is made up of a large variety of international connections and if you are visiting this website the various communications may well result in the transfer of information outside the European Economic Area other than pursuant to contractual arrangements made by us. By visiting the website and communicating electronically with us you consent to these transfers. All sensitive player data is protected in accordance with the Data Protection Law (Bailiwick of Guernsey) 2001. In addition, paddypowercasino.com consults the EU privacy laws and the OECD guidelines regularly to ensure the protection of players privacy and transborder data flow. 

If you do not wish to receive promotional or other information then please check the appropriate box during the registration process. 

For further information on what data is held about you can be obtained by contacting Us as follows - 

Paddy Power Gaming Support  
Airton House  
Airton Road  
Tallaght  
Dublin 24 

With the exception of your personal details, all other information, including, but not limited to, ideas, submissions, emails, suggestions, concepts, graphics, chatroom contents including material and statements, posted on this site or submitted to us will become our property and we shall not be subject to any obligation of confidentiality and will be free to reproduce, modify, edit, adapt, publish, translate, distribute and display by Us or anyone we designate in any and all media now known or in the future created. 

This Our Promise forms part of our website Terms and Conditions and as such it shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of England. You irrevocably agree that the courts of England and Wales shall have exclusive jurisdiction to resolve any dispute or claim of whatever nature arising out of or relating to this policy and consent or otherwise to the use of your personal data, and that the laws of England shall govern such dispute or claim. However, we retain the right to bring legal proceedings in any jurisdiction where we believe that infringement of our intellectual property rights or breach of those terms is taking place or originating. 

You are responsible for compliance with any applicable laws and regulations of the jurisdiction from which you are accessing this website. We operate this website from Alderney and make no representation or warranty that the information contained herein is appropriate or available for use in other locations outside Alderney.
